Guide to the George McTurnan Kahin papers, [ca. 1945-2000]
Kahin, George McTurnan papers, [ca. 1945-2000]
- Series VII. Administration
  - General Administration & Research
    - Finances, 1964-65 (Box 47, Folder 58)
    - Rockefeller: University of the Philippines, 1963-64 (Box 47, Folder 59)
    - Rockefeller-International Relations, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 60)
    - Possbile Cornell-University of Phil., Affilitation, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 61)
    - Asian Studies, 1963-68 (Box 47, Folder 62)
    - Ford-Phil, 1964-65 (Box 47, Folder 63)
    - Rockefeller, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 64)
    - Trip-Rockefeller, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 65)
    - Interview-Manila, 1965-66 (Box 47, Folder 66)
    - Political Theory, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 67)
    - Germany-Nazi, 1940-41 (Box 47, Folder 68)
    - Chinese in Indonesia, Political Position, M.A. Thesis-Stanford University, June 1946, 1946 (Box 47, Folder 69)
    - Addresses, 1964 (Box 47, Folder 70)
    - College of Arts and Sciences, 1964-65 (Box 47, Folder 71)
    - Ford-10 Year Proposals, 1951-60 (Box 47, Folder 72)
    - Course Outlines, 1952-61 (Box 47, Folder 73)
    - Government: China Specialist, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 74)
    - Soviet Affairs, 1960 (Box 47, Folder 75)
    - Soviet Foreign Policy, 1961 (Box 47, Folder 76)
    - International Relations, 1960-61 (Box 47, Folder 77)
    - Public Administration, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 78)
    - NDEA: Comparative Government and International Relations, 1961 (Box 47, Folder 79)
    - New Curriculum, 1961 (Box 47, Folder 80)
    - Government Department Regulations, 1962-64 (Box 47, Folder 81)
    - Enrollment Figures, 1959-61 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Government Department, 1964-65 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Government Department, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Government Department, 1965-66 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Government Honors, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Government Honors, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Government Department, 1957-58 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Activities, 1954-59 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Government: Personal, 1951-61 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Government-Miscellaneous, 1954-61 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Salary Scales, 1961-65 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Library, 1958-64 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Personnel-Cornell, 1959-63 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - SEAP-Current, 1961-63 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - SEAP, 1957-60 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - FES-SEAP Budgets, 1951-59 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - SEAP-M.A. Theses, 1962 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - S.E.A. Program, 1957-61 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - SEAP Budget, 1957-59 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Ford, 1954-56 (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - SEAP Finances, 1955-58 (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - Ford: Cornell-SEA, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - SEAP Ford-Emergency Fund ($5900), 1957-58 (Box 48, Folder 23)
    - SEAP-Data Papers, 1957 (Box 48, Folder 24)
    - Personnel, 1960-61 (Box 48, Folder 25)
    - Fellowships, 1959-64 (Box 48, Folder 26)
    - Southeast Asian-Historian, 1960-61 (Box 48, Folder 27)
    - SEA-Courses, 1964-65 (Box 48, Folder 28)
    - Student Enrollment Report, 1961 (Box 48, Folder 29)
    - Far Eastern Studies, 1957-61 (Box 48, Folder 30)
    - FES: Grad. Students, 1958-61 (Box 48, Folder 31)
    - F.E.S. Minor, 1961 (Box 48, Folder 32)
    - Subscriptions (SEAP), 1964 (Box 48, Folder 33)
    - SEAP Graduate Students Field Research Report, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 34)
    - SEAP Luncheon Meetings, 1963-64 (Box 48, Folder 35)
    - NDEA, 1961-63 (Box 48, Folder 36)
    - Soviet Exchange, 1962-64 (Box 48, Folder 37)
    - SEAPS Fellowships, 1964-65 (Box 48, Folder 38)
    - SEAP Memorandum, 1963-64 (Box 48, Folder 39)
    - SEAP Students, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 40)
    - Travel, 1954-57 (Box 48, Folder 41)
    - Trips, 1960-61 (Box 48, Folder 42)
    - Trip-Summer, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 43)
    - Travel, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 44)
    - Travel Expenses, 1954-59 (Box 48, Folder 45)
    - Cornell University, 1956-59 (Box 48, Folder 46)
    - University Affairs, 1954-55 (Box 48, Folder 47)
    - Racial Discrimination, 1961 (Box 48, Folder 48)
    - Foreign Students, 1957-61 (Box 48, Folder 49)
    - Hall Fund, 1960-63 (Box 48, Folder 50)
    - American Academy of A & S, 1970 (Box 48, Folder 51)
    - Spiegel & Waltz, 1970 (Box 48, Folder 52)
    - Division of Modern Languages, 1967-71 (Box 48, Folder 53)
    - Asia Society, 1967-72 (Box 48, Folder 54)
    - China-Salzburg, 1945 (Box 48, Folder 55)
    - Confidential-References and Recommendations on Students Miscellaneous, 1957-58 (Box 48, Folder 56)
    - Active, 1976-1979 (Box 48, Folder 57)
    - Terminations, 1968-77 (Box 48, Folder 58)
    - Personnel-Burma, 1970 (Box 48, Folder 59)
    - Terminations-Pre 1961, 1956-60 (Box 48, Folder 60)
    - Personnel, 1979-80 (Box 48, Folder 61)
    - Publications-Procedure, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 62)
    - DWL Payroll, 1971-73 (Box 48, Folder 63)
    - Personnel Blank Forms & Direction, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 64)
    - Finances-London, 1962-63 (Box 48, Folder 65)
    - Inventory: June 3, 1957, 1957 (Box 48, Folder 66)
    - Inventory, 1968-70 (Box 48, Folder 67)
    - Micro Film-Dan, 1962-64 (Box 48, Folder 68)
    - Inventory, 1956-66 (Box 48, Folder 69)
- Series VIII. Indonesia
  - Trip-April 1967 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Indonesia, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Trip: December '69 - February '70 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Trip (Jan 1970) Personal Receipts, 1969-70 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Trip: 1970-71 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Talk to Ben's Class, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - BBC/Carey, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Reading Lists on Indonesia & Bibliographies, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Japanese Occupation, 1956-74 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Interviews (mostly filed elsewhere), 1945-49 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Letters & DNA Dispatches, 1948-49 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Indonesia-Notes, 1948-49 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Front National-Indonesia, 1948 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Front National-Indonesia (continued), 1948 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Indonesia: McArthur, 1945-46 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Deutch Army, 1945-46 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Indonesia-Post Zegels (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - PhD Jessup, 1948-49 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Truman Indonesia, 1950 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Year 1951 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - MSA, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - U.S. Policy-Indonesia, 1949 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Indonesia: 1971 Duplicate of Interviews (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Interviews: 1970-71 Complete List, 1970-72 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Indonesia Djakarta, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Indonesia-Sumatra, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Indonesia, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Visa Memorandum, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - Notes-Indonesia, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - Guided Democracy Reasons for, 1959-60 (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - U.S. & Indonesia-General, 1956-61 (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - Algadri, Hamid, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 32)
  - Bali, 1948-49 (Box 49, Folder 33)
  - BBC, 1948-49 (Box 49, Folder 34)
  - Indonesia: Circle April 26, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 35)
  - Indonesia: Talk on Personal Experiences, Oct. 7, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 36)
  - 102 West Ave: May 5, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 38)
  - Bunnell-Subandrio, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - Bunnell-Eisenhower, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 40)
  - Bunnell: NSC-Indonesia, 1976-77 (Box 49, Folder 41)
  - Bunnell, 1975-77 (Box 49, Folder 42)
  - Bunnell, 1976-77 (Box 49, Folder 43)
  - Indonesia-Kennedy, 1973-75 (Box 49, Folder 44)
  - Inventory of Documents and Office Files, 1961 (Box 49, Folder 45)
  - Inventory of Documents-National Security FIles, 1961-63 (Box 49, Folder 46)
  - John F. Kennedy Library-Files on Indonesia, 1961 (Box 49, Folder 47)
  - Indonesia: Bunker Visit and Followup, 1976-77 (Box 49, Folder 48)
  - Indonesia: Assessment of the Coup, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 49)
  - Indonesia-Anit-U.S. Provocations, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 50)
  - Indonesia: The Succession Problem, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 51)
  - Indonesia: Hints of US Retaliation of Involement in Coup, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 52)
  - Indonesia: Sukarno's Health, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 53)
  - Indonesia: US Military Aid, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 54)
  - LBJ: Indonesia, 1965-80 (Box 49, Folder 55)
  - January 1965: Imp. (Box 49, Folder 56)
  - Indonesia: Pre Coup Rel with U.S., 1975 (Box 49, Folder 57)
  - Indonesia-G.K., 1965-66 (Box 49, Folder 58)
  - Indonesia-The Coup, 1965-75 (Box 49, Folder 59)
  - U.S. - Oct. 21, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 60)
  - Indonesia, 1965-76 (Box 49, Folder 61)
  - Indonesia: Post Coup Rel w/ U.S., 1965 (Box 49, Folder 62)
  - Jones-State: Jan. 21, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 63)
  - Hatta, 1949-81 (Box 49, Folder 64)
  - Hatta (continued), 1949-60 (Box 49, Folder 65)
  - Hatta Articles, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 66)
  - Jones-Indon to McGraw, 1958 (Box 49, Folder 67)
  - Nasution, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 68)
  - Masjumi Article, 1977-79 (Box 49, Folder 69)
  - Mohammad Roem & Mohammad Nastir, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 70)
  - Nastir-Roem Correspondence, 1977-78 (Box 49, Folder 71)
  - Pamphlets-Indonesia, 1938-1957 (Box 49, Folder 72)
  - Pamphlets-Indonesia (continued), 1952-57 (Box 49, Folder 73)
  - M. Roem, 1980-84 (Box 49, Folder 74)
  - Masjumi, 1979-80 (Box 49, Folder 75)
  - Palar, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 76)
  - Sultan of Jogjakarta, 1948-54 (Box 49, Folder 77)
  - The Sultan and the Dutch, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 78)
  - H.A. Salim, 1952-84 (Box 49, Folder 79)
  - Roem re Sjafruddin, 1980-89 (Box 49, Folder 80)
  - U.N. Good Offices Comm.-Indonesia, 1947-48 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Sjahrir, 1948-66 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Sjahrir, 1945-80 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Maria Ullfah Suebadio, 1988-89 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Bibliography: Indonesia, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Indonesia: GAO, 1978-79 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Ben & Ruth: NY Review of Books, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Neville Maxwell, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Peter Dali Scott, 1984 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Thomas Maas: "Manhunt", 1986 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Ben's 387 Lecture: April 29, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Ben's Testimony: Feb. 15, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Ben's Testimony: Feb. 6, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Islam, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Indonesia, 1979-86 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - U.S. Policy, 1977-78 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Current U.S. Policy, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Memorandum: Indonesia & U.S.-Indonesian Relations (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Eqbal Ahmed: May 23, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Rendra: Indonesian Human Right's Article, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Indonesia: Duplicates, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Indonesia: Misc. Articles & Reports, 1975-78 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Kohen, 1977-79 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Indonesia, 1977-78 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Student "White Book", 1978 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - U.S. Econ + M.1 Ass't, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Oakley, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - Faser Comm., 1977-78 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Indonesia: Wash. Packet, 1976-77 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - Deliar Noer, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - Econ. Development Controversy, 1974-75 (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - Nasution-Vietnam, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 32)
  - Navy, 1973-74 (Box 50, Folder 33)
  - Tanaka Riots, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 34)
  - Soeharto-Jenkins: Sydney Morning Herald, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 35)
  - Ideas on 1965 Coup, 1988 (Box 50, Folder 36)
  - Suwarto Interviews, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 37)
  - Ruth, Sept. 1977-81 (Box 50, Folder 38)
  - Jones-Nasution: March 6, 1964 (Box 50, Folder 39)
  - Possible British Provocation, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 40)
  - Nasution, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 41)
  - Richard Dudley, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 42)
  - David Johnson, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 43)
  - Coup Interpretations-Current, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 44)
  - Monthly Review: Flangan & Southwood, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 45)
  - TAPOL: U.S. Response to Tanka Riots, 1974-75 (Box 50, Folder 46)
  - Geertz, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 47)
  - Soenardi: Dec. 1981 (Box 50, Folder 48)
  - Indonesia, 1986-88 (Box 50, Folder 49)
  - Indonesia-Political Prisoners, 1975-78 (Box 50, Folder 50)
  - Indonesia, 1982-86 (Box 50, Folder 51)
  - U.S. Ambassador to Jakarta, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 52)
  - Timor, 1980-82 (Box 50, Folder 53)
  - Ramparts Article (and ltrs), 1970 (Box 50, Folder 54)
  - Research
    - Indonesia Research: 102 West Ave, Oct. 7, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - G.K. in Indonesia-102 West Ave, 1948-49 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Colonial Background, 1940-60 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Digul, 1945-55 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Japanese Occupation I, 1956-60 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Japanese Occupation II, 1948-55 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Nishijima, 1958-59 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Japanese Occupation: Microfilm from Mr. Kishi, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Japanese Occupation, 1955-58 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Pre-Colonial Background, 1958 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Administration: Regional and Local I, 1959-61 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Administration: Regional and Local II, 1960's (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Decree Administration Indonesia in the Transiton Period, 1945 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Historical Background (Pre-Revolutionary), 1933-61 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Nationalist Movement, 1960 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Social Background, 1950 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - History of Indonesian Nationalism before 1942 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Japanese Occupation, 1940-45 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Indonesian Army, 1945-48 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Linggadjati, 1946-49 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - U.S. & Indonesia, 1949-59 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Econ. Policy-Dutch, 1945-49 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Monthly Economic Review, 1949 (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - Letters Commenting on G's Book, 1952 (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - Indonesian Rep. Propaganda from Indonesian Groups Outside Indonesia, 1945-49 (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - Reactions to Nationalsim and Revolution, 1952-54 (Box 51, Folder 26)
    - Nationalism, 1949 (Box 51, Folder 27)
    - Economic Conditions, 1956-1963 (Box 51, Folder 28)
    - Political Behavior, 1951-57 (Box 51, Folder 29)
    - Decision Making, 1951-59 (Box 51, Folder 30)
    - New York Times, 1959-60 (Box 51, Folder 31)
    - Structure of Power, 1945 (Box 51, Folder 32)
    - Problems, 1955-63 (Box 51, Folder 33)
    - Civil Liberties, 1926-49 (Box 51, Folder 34)
    - Cabinet, 1945-66 (Box 51, Folder 35)
    - Political Manifesto, 1945-46 (Box 51, Folder 36)
    - Political Forces, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 37)
    - Press and Public Opinion, 1958 (Box 51, Folder 38)
    - Parliament, 1945-58 (Box 51, Folder 39)
    - Elections, 1955-56 (Box 51, Folder 40)
    - Sumatra-Tengah, 1956-58 (Box 51, Folder 41)
      Contains 1955 election regional results. Results for other provinces across Indonesia, not just Central Sumatra, broken down by candidate, region and sub-district.
    - Parties, 1954-60 (Box 51, Folder 42)
    - P.N.I., 1947-48 (Box 51, Folder 43)
    - Education, 1948-59 (Box 51, Folder 44)
    - Labor, 1947-53 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Social Services, 1948-51 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Indonesia: Communism-Bibliography (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Women, 1948 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Communism Post-Madiun Indonesia, 1954-60 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Communism-Pre-War Indonesia, 1948-49 (Box 52, Folder 6-7)
    - Communism, U.S.S.R., Indonesia, 1952 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Bandung Technical School, 1924 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Police Institute Indonesia, 1955 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Communism Indonesia I, 1951-60 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Communism Indonesia II, 1947-53 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Communism Indonesia III, 1955-60 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - P.K.I., 1958-63 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Labor, 1958 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Press Reviews, 1948-49 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Roem Van Royen, 1948-49 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Dissatisfaction with Roem Van Royen, 1949 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Dutch Policy, 1946-49 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Dutch Propaganda, 1945-49 (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Atrocities: Dutch Press, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - 1947-Netherlands Sources Re Negotiations, Fighting, Etc. I, 1946-47 (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - 1947-Netherlands Sources Re Negotiations, Fighting, Etc. II (Box 52, Folder 23)
    - U.S. Troop Transports to Jauz-Sholte on British Role, 1945-46 (Box 52, Folder 24)
    - Dec. 1947: Split in Socialist Party, 1945-48 (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - Important Interviews, 1948-49 (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - Interviews, 1948-49 (Box 52, Folder 27)
    - Dutch Views: On Oranje-Dr.Van Mooke, Koets, 1948 (Box 52, Folder 28)
    - Attack on Jogja: Dec. 19, 1948 (Box 52, Folder 29)
    - Indonesia: Hooge Veluwe, 1946 (Box 52, Folder 30)
    - Negotiations, 1945-49 (Box 52, Folder 31)
    - Negotiations, 1948-49 (Box 52, Folder 32)
    - Post December 19, 1948, 1949 (Box 52, Folder 33)
    - Frank Graham Interview I, 1963 (Box 52, Folder 34)
    - Frank Graham, 1950 (Box 52, Folder 35)
    - Darsono, 1950-57 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - John Griffin: A.P. Correspondence, 1961 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Hatta: (April 27) Speech, 1957-58 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Hatta on Madiun, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Hatta: 1960 at Cornell (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Hatta, 1957-58 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Hatta, 1948-56 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Ali Budiardjo, 1959 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Gould, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - D.N. Aidit, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Hatta, 1949-55 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Hatta: September 2, 1948 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Hatta, 1949-60 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - A, Gafar Pringgodigdo, 1948-55 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Roeslan Abdoelgani, 1948-60 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Hadji Salim Lectures, 1953 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Hadji Salim, 1948-54 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Ali Sastromidjojo, 1948 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Soebardjo, December 1948 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Sitorus, 1947-51 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Simatupang, 1957-70 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - Sjahrir, 1958-61 (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - Sjahrir: Consequences of PRRI & Paving Way for 1965, 1958-61 (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - Soekarno, 1945-59 (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - Pringgodigdo on Sukarno, 1958-59 (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - Sukarno, 1948-63 (Box 53, Folder 26)
    - Sukarno: August 17, 1945-Proclamation of Indonesia Independence (Box 53, Folder 27)
    - Sukarno: Duplicates, 1945-49 (Box 53, Folder 28)
    - Sukarno-Madiun: September 19, 1948 (Box 53, Folder 29)
    - Dr. Sukiman-Interview with Jogjakarta, 1948 (Box 53, Folder 30)
    - Sukarno: September 1948 (Box 53, Folder 31)
    - Sukarno-November, 1948-49 (Box 53, Folder 32)
    - Sukarno Correspondence to G.K., 1954 (Box 53, Folder 33)
    - Suripno-Member and leader of Communist Party & Indonesian Rep. at Prague, 1948 (Box 53, Folder 34)
    - Sukarno Correspondence, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 35)
    - Sukarno & Disfraction Thesis, 1947 (Box 53, Folder 36)
    - Transcript: President Sukarno's Interview with CBS, Jan. 31, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 37)
    - Sukarno: Memorandum & Speech before the Council of World Affairs, 1961 (Box 53, Folder 38)
    - Sukarno: 1954, 1955 Interviews, 1954-58 (Box 53, Folder 39)
    - Indonesia: Notes, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 40)
    - Indonesia-Notes-G.K., 1954-55 (Box 53, Folder 41)
    - President Soekarno's Visit to the United States, 1956-63 (Box 53, Folder 42)
    - Soekarno's Speeches Affecting U.S. View, 1956-57 (Box 53, Folder 43)
    - Dec. 19, 1948-Undeveloped Speeches of Sukarno-Hatta-Natsir (Box 53, Folder 44)
    - Madiun, 1926-49 (Box 53, Folder 45)
    - Musso-Djalan Baru, 1948 (Box 53, Folder 46)
    - Alimin Analysis-April 1947 (Box 53, Folder 47)
    - Interviews: Indonesia (Duplicate Copies), 1948 (Box 53, Folder 48)
    - Indonesia-Photographs, 1948 (Box 53, Folder 49)
    - Soekarno-Interviews, 1948-49 (Box 53, Folder 50)
    - Asia Society-Koko, May 29, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 51)
    - Soedjatmoko-Obituary etc., 1959-90 (Box 53, Folder 52)
    - Soedjatmoko-Correspondence & Article, 1990-91 (Box 53, Folder 53)
    - Soedjatmoko: Asia Society, May 29, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 54)
    - Soedjatmoko-Historiopraphy Symposium (maps), 1964 (Box 53, Folder 55)
    - Suripno, 1948 (Box 53, Folder 56)
    - Indonesia: Articles, 1943-55 (Box 53, Folder 57)
    - Renville, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 58)
    - Economic Data in Newspapers, 1945-49 (Box 53, Folder 59)
    - Sultan of Jogjakarta, 1949-56 (Box 53, Folder 60)
    - Indonesia-Soekarno I, 1945-59 (Box 53, Folder 61)
    - Indonesia-Soekarno II, 1945-59 (Box 53, Folder 62)
    - Indonesia-Soekarno III, 1945-59 (Box 53, Folder 63)
    - Soekarno & the President, 1948-59 (Box 53, Folder 64)
    - Soekarno Translation, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 65)
    - Sukarno (Translation by Molly Bondan-6th Chapter Sarinah), 1953 (Box 53, Folder 66)
    - Army I, 1948-56 (Box 53, Folder 67)
    - Army II, 1952-96 (Box 53, Folder 68)
    - Bureaucracy, 1950-60 (Box 53, Folder 69)
    - Pamong Pradja, 1920-57 (Box 53, Folder 70)
    - Islamic State, 1953 (Box 53, Folder 71)
    - Ideology, 1961 (Box 53, Folder 72)
    - Local Government-Village and Intermediate, 1951-57 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Laws: Acts, 1945-48 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Constitutional Law-Indonesia, 1947-54 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Madiun, 1947-60 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Madiun Documents, 1948-58 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - State Council, 1948-49 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - K.N.I.P., 1947 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Local Government-Indonesia, 1955 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Politics-Republic, 1948-54 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Village Organization-Indonesia, 1948 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Antara-Indonesia, 1948 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Arrest of Tan Malaka-Recording to AB Lubis, 1946 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - 1948 Material on villages not transferred to Keysort (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Constitutions I, 1950-57 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Constitutions II, 1953 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Masjumi, 1948-57 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Roem, Moh'd, 1957-59 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - 1945 Constitution and Background, 1945-49 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Resistance, 1948-49 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Ministry of Religion-Indonesia, 1953-55 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - P.N.I., 1948-56 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - P.S.I.I., 1948-49 (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Front Nasional, 1948 (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Yogya Press, 1948-56 (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Press-Jogja & Madiun, 1948 (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Madiun, 1948 (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - Madiun Rebellion, 1948-49 (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - Madiun Rebellion, 1960-61 (Box 76, Folder 30)
    - McVey/Madiun-"Communist Policy and the Madiun Affair", 1955 (Box 54, Folder 28)
    - FDR, 1948 (Box 54, Folder 29)
    - Front Nasional I, 1948 (Box 54, Folder 30)
    - Front Nasional II, 1948 (Box 54, Folder 31)
    - Madiun, 1948-61 (Box 54, Folder 32)
    - Communist Rebel, 1948-55 (Box 54, Folder 33)
    - Communist Government-Madiun, 1948 (Box 54, Folder 34)
    - Newspaper Translations, 1948-49 (Box 54, Folder 35)
    - Indonesia: Political, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 36)
    - MSA Affair, 1952-60 (Box 54, Folder 37)
    - Political-Indonesia, 1949 (Box 54, Folder 38)
    - Rep. Ind. Serikat Politics, 1949 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Political-Indonesia, 1950-55 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Republik Indonesia-Economics, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Government Rep. of Indonesia, 1950-57 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Decision Making-Indonesia, 1958-59 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Soekarno: Indonesia Menggugat (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Interviews, 1948-49 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Representation (and lack of) Authority, 1961-64 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Population, 1955-61 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Chinese I, 1946-1959 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Chinese II, 1948-59 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Chinese III, 1949-61 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Chinese-Kartomo, 1957 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Chinese in Indonesia, 1948 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Schmitt, Hans O.-Foreign Capital and Monetary Instability in Indonesia, 1950-58 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Alex Shakow-Prospects of Democracy in Southeast Asia, 1950-61 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Alex Shakow-"Foreign Economic Assistance in Indonesia", 1950-61 (Box 55, Folder 17)